Guide to the Walt Horan Papers 1939-1967
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 4: Departmental, 1943-1964
  - Production and Marketing Administration
    - 1953 (Box 163, Folder 4465)
    - 1954 (Box 163, Folder 4466-4467)
    - 1953 (Box 163, Folder 4468)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 163, Folder 4469)
  - Railroad Retirement: 1944-1952
    - 1952 (Box 164, Folder 4470)
    - 1951 (Box 164, Folder 4471-4472)
    - 1950 (Box 164, Folder 4473)
    - 1949 (Box 164, Folder 4474)
    - 1948 (Box 164, Folder 4475)
    - 1948 (Box 164, Folder 4476)
    - 1947 (Box 164, Folder 4477-4479)
    - 1945 (Box 164, Folder 4480-4481)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 164, Folder 4482)
  - Railroad Retirement: 1953-1964
    - 1963 (Box 165, Folder 4483)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 165, Folder 4484)
    - 1959 (Box 165, Folder 4485-4487)
    - 1958 (Box 165, Folder 4488-4492)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 165, Folder 4493)
    - 1956 (Box 165, Folder 4494)
    - 1955 (Box 165, Folder 4495)
    - 1954 (Box 165, Folder 4496-4497)
    - 1953 (Box 165, Folder 4498)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation
    - 1955 (Box 166, Folder 4499)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 166, Folder 4500)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 166, Folder 4501)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 166, Folder 4502)
    - 1950 (Box 166, Folder 4503)
    - 1949 (Box 166, Folder 4504)
    - 1948 (Box 166, Folder 4505)
    - 1947 (Box 166, Folder 4506)
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation: Regional Agricultural Credit Corporation, 1943-1948
    - 1948 (Box 166, Folder 4507)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 166, Folder 4508)
    - 1944 (Box 166, Folder 4509)
    - 1943 (Box 166, Folder 4510-4512)
    - 1944 (Box 166, Folder 4513-4514)
    - 1943 (Box 166, Folder 4515-4516)
  - Rural Electrification Administration
    - 1945 (Box 167, Folder 4517)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 167, Folder 4518)
    - 1952 (Box 167, Folder 4519)
    - 1951 (Box 167, Folder 4520-4521)
    - 1950 (Box 167, Folder 4522-4523)
    - 1949 (Box 167, Folder 4524)
    - 1948 (Box 167, Folder 4525)
    - 1947 (Box 167, Folder 4526-4527)
    - 1958 (Box 167, Folder 4528-4529)
    - 1956 (Box 168, Folder 4530)
    - 1957 (Box 168, Folder 4531)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 168, Folder 4532)
    - 1954 (Box 168, Folder 4533)
    - 1953 (Box 168, Folder 4534)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 168, Folder 4535)
    - 1963 (Box 168, Folder 4536)
    - 1962 (Box 168, Folder 4537)
    - 1961 (Box 168, Folder 4538)
    - 1960 (Box 168, Folder 4539)
    - 1959 (Box 168, Folder 4540-4542)
  - Securities Exchange Commission
    - 1957 (Box 169, Folder 4543)
    - 1953 (Box 169, Folder 4544)
    - 1952 (Box 169, Folder 4545-4546)
    - 1947-1949 (Box 169, Folder 4547)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 169, Folder 4548)
    - 1964 (Box 169, Folder 4549)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 169, Folder 4550)
    - 1957 (Box 169, Folder 4551)
    - 1956 (Box 169, Folder 4552-4553)
  - Social Security Administration
    - 1950 (Box 169, Folder 4554-4557)
    - 1949 (Box 169, Folder 4558-4559)
    - 1949 (continued) (Box 170, Folder 4560-4561)
    - 1948 (Box 170, Folder 4562-4565)
    - 1947 (Box 170, Folder 4566-4567)
    - 1945 (Box 170, Folder 4568)
    - 1944 (Box 170, Folder 4569)
    - 1943 (Box 170, Folder 4570-4571)
    - 1956 (Box 170, Folder 4572-4574)
    - 1955 (Box 170, Folder 4575)
    - 1954-4579 (Box 171, Folder 4576)
    - 1953 (Box 171, Folder 4580-4582)
    - 1952 (Box 171, Folder 4583-4584)
    - 1951 (Box 171, Folder 4585)
    - 1959 (Box 171, Folder 4586-4589)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 171, Folder 4590)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 172, Folder 4591)
    - 1958 (Box 172, Folder 4592-4597)
    - 1957 (Box 172, Folder 4598-4601)
    - 1964 (Box 172, Folder 4602)
    - 1962-1964 (Box 172, Folder 4603)
    - 1961 (Box 172, Folder 4604)
    - 1960 (Box 172, Folder 4605)
    - 1964 (Box 173, Folder 4606)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 173, Folder 4607)
    - 1962 (Box 173, Folder 4608-4609)
    - 1961 (Box 173, Folder 4610)
    - 1960 (Box 173, Folder 4611-4612)
  - State Department
    - 1950 (Box 173, Folder 4613)
    - 1949 (Box 173, Folder 4614)
    - 1948 (Box 173, Folder 4615-4616)
    - 1949 (Box 173, Folder 4617)
    - 1948 (Box 173, Folder 4618)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 174, Folder 4619)
    - 1947 (Box 174, Folder 4620-4622)
    - 1946 (Box 174, Folder 4623-4624)
    - 1945 (Box 174, Folder 4625)
    - 1943 (Box 174, Folder 4626-4627)
    - 1950 (Box 174, Folder 4628)
    - 1948 (Box 174, Folder 4629)
    - 1950 (Box 174, Folder 4630)
    - 1949 (Box 174, Folder 4631)
    - 1950 (Box 174, Folder 4632-4633)
    - 1954 (Box 175, Folder 4634-4635)
    - 1953 (Box 175, Folder 4636)
    - 1947-1952 (Box 175, Folder 4637)
    - 1953 (Box 175, Folder 4638)
    - 1952 (Box 175, Folder 4639)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 175, Folder 4640)
    - 1952 (Box 175, Folder 4641-4643)
    - 1951 (Box 175, Folder 4644)
    - 1950 (Box 175, Folder 4645)
    - 1946-1950 (Box 175, Folder 4646)
    - 1952 (Box 175, Folder 4647-4649)
    - 1951 (Box 175, Folder 4650)
    - 1958 (Box 176, Folder 4651-4654)
    - 1957 (Box 176, Folder 4655-4659)
    - 1956 (Box 176, Folder 4660-4664)
    - 1955 (Box 176, Folder 4665-4668)
    - 1954 (Box 176, Folder 4669)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 176, Folder 4670)
    - 1961 (Box 177, Folder 4671-4675)
    - 1960 (Box 177, Folder 4676-4678)
    - 1959 (Box 177, Folder 4679-4687)
    - 1958 (Box 177, Folder 4688)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 178, Folder 4689)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 178, Folder 4690)
    - 1963 (Box 178, Folder 4691-4699)
    - 1962 (Box 178, Folder 4700-4711)
    - 1944 (Box 179, Folder 4712)
    - 1964 (Box 179, Folder 4713-4717)
  - Townsend Plan
    - 1960-1962 (Box 179, Folder 4718)
    - 1959 (Box 179, Folder 4719)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 179, Folder 4720)
    - 1956 (Box 179, Folder 4721)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 179, Folder 4722)
    - 1953 (Box 179, Folder 4723-4724)
    - 1952 (Box 179, Folder 4725)
    - 1951 (Box 179, Folder 4726)
    - 1950 (Box 179, Folder 4727)
    - 1949 (Box 179, Folder 4728)
    - 1948 (Box 179, Folder 4729-4730)
    - 1947 (Box 179, Folder 4731-4732)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 179, Folder 4733)
    - 1943 (Box 179, Folder 4734-4735)
  - U.S. Information Agency
    - 1964 (Box 180, Folder 4736)
    - 1963 (Box 180, Folder 4737)
    - 1962 (Box 180, Folder 4738)
    - 1961 (Box 180, Folder 4739)
    - 1960 (Box 180, Folder 4740-4741)
    - 1956-1959 (Box 180, Folder 4742)
  - Veterans' Administration
    - 1943 (Box 180, Folder 4743-4748)
    - 1944 (Box 180, Folder 4749-4750)
    - 1960 (Box 180, Folder 4751-4755)
    - 1960 (continued) (Box 181, Folder 4756-4758)
    - 1959 (Box 181, Folder 4759-4766)
    - 1950 (Box 181, Folder 4767-4771)
    - 1949 (Box 181, Folder 4772)
    - 1949 (continued) (Box 182, Folder 4773-4776)
    - 1948 (Box 182, Folder 4777-4780)
    - 1947 (Box 182, Folder 4781-4787)
  - G.I. Legislation
    - 1945 (Box 182, Folder 4791)
    - 1944 (Box 182, Folder 4792-4793)
  - Veterans Legislation
    - 1951 (Box 183, Folder 4794-4795)
    - 1952 (Box 183, Folder 4796-4798)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 183, Folder 4799)
    - 1954 (Box 183, Folder 4800-4803)
    - 1955 (Box 183, Folder 4804-4806)
    - 1956 (Box 183, Folder 4807-4811)
    - 1957 (Box 183, Folder 4812)
    - 1951 (Box 184, Folder 4813)
    - 1957 (Box 184, Folder 4814-4816)
    - 1958 (Box 184, Folder 4817-4819)
    - 1961 (Box 184, Folder 4820-4829)
    - 1962 (Box 184, Folder 4830)
    - 1962 (continued) (Box 185, Folder 4831-4835)
    - 1964 (Box 185, Folder 4836-4840)
    - 1963 (Box 185, Folder 4841-4844)
  - Veterans' Cases
    - 1947-1948: A (Box 186, Folder 4845)
    - 1947-1948: B (Box 186, Folder 4846)
    - 1947-1948: C (Box 186, Folder 4847)
    - 1947-1948: C-F (Box 186, Folder 4848)
    - 1947-1948: H-I (Box 186, Folder 4849)
    - 1947-1948: J (Box 186, Folder 4850)
    - 1947-1948: J (Box 186, Folder 4851)
    - 1947-1948: A-G (Box 186, Folder 4852)
    - 1947-1948: H-O (Box 186, Folder 4853)
    - 1947-1948: P-R (Box 186, Folder 4854)
    - 1947-1948: S (Box 186, Folder 4855)
    - 1947-1948: U-V (Box 186, Folder 4856)
    - 1947-1948: W (Box 186, Folder 4857)
    - 1947-1948: W (Box 186, Folder 4858)
    - 1946: A-B (Box 186, Folder 4859)
    - 1946: C (Box 187, Folder 4860)
    - 1946: D-G (Box 187, Folder 4861)
    - 1946: H-M (Box 187, Folder 4862)
    - 1946: O (Box 187, Folder 4863)
    - 1946: P-R (Box 187, Folder 4864)
    - 1946: S-T (Box 187, Folder 4865)
    - 1946: V-Z (Box 187, Folder 4866)
    - 1947-1948: K-L (Box 187, Folder 4867)
    - 1947-1948: M (Box 187, Folder 4868-4869)
    - 1949-1951: A (Box 187, Folder 4870)
    - 1949-1951: B (Box 187, Folder 4871)
    - 1949-1951: C (Box 187, Folder 4872)
    - 1949-1951: D (Box 187, Folder 4873)
    - 1949-1951: E-G (Box 187, Folder 4874A)
    - 1949-1951: H (Box 187, Folder 4874B-4874D)
    - 1949-1951: I (Box 188, Folder 4875)
    - 1949-1951: J-K (Box 188, Folder 4876)
    - 1949-1951: L (Box 188, Folder 4877)
    - 1949-1951: M (Box 188, Folder 4878-4879)
    - 1949-1951: N-P (Box 188, Folder 4880)
    - 1949-1951: R (Box 188, Folder 4881)
    - 1949-1951: S (Box 188, Folder 4882)
    - 1949-1951: T (Box 188, Folder 4883)
    - 1949-1951: U-V (Box 188, Folder 4884)
    - 1949-1951: W (Box 188, Folder 4885)
    - 1949-1951: Z (Box 188, Folder 4886)
    - 1952-1954: A-B (Box 188, Folder 4887)
    - 1952-1954: B-C (Box 188, Folder 4888)
    - 1952-1954: D-F (Box 188, Folder 4889)
    - 1952-1954: G (Box 189, Folder 4890)
    - 1952-1954: H (Box 189, Folder 4891)
    - 1952-1954: J-L (Box 189, Folder 4892)
    - 1952-1954: M (Box 189, Folder 4893)
    - 1952-1954: N-R (Box 189, Folder 4894)
    - 1952-1954: S (Box 189, Folder 4895)
    - 1952-1954: T (Box 189, Folder 4896)
    - 1952-1954: V (Box 189, Folder 4897)
    - 1952-1954: W (Box 189, Folder 4898)
    - 1952-1954: Y (Box 189, Folder 4899)
    - 1955-1957: A (Box 189, Folder 4900)
    - 1955-1957: C (Box 189, Folder 4901-4902)
    - 1955-1957: D (Box 189, Folder 4903)
    - 1955-1957: G (Box 189, Folder 4904)
    - 1955-1957: H (Box 189, Folder 4905-4906)
    - 1955-1957: J-K (Box 189, Folder 4907)
    - 1955-1957: L (Box 190, Folder 4908)
    - 1955-1957: M (Box 190, Folder 4909-4910)
    - 1955-1957: N-P (Box 190, Folder 4911)
    - 1955-1957: R (Box 190, Folder 4912)
    - 1955-1957: S (Box 190, Folder 4913-4914)
    - 1955-1957: T (Box 190, Folder 4915)
    - 1955-1957: W (Box 190, Folder 4916-4917)
    - 1958-1960: A-B (Box 190, Folder 4918)
    - 1958-1960: C (Box 190, Folder 4919)
    - 1958-1960: F-G (Box 190, Folder 4920)
    - 1958-1960: H (Box 190, Folder 4921)
    - 1958-1960: J (Box 191, Folder 4922)
    - 1958-1960: K-L (Box 191, Folder 4923)
    - 1958-1960: M (Box 191, Folder 4924)
    - 1958-1960: M (Box 191, Folder 4925)
    - 1958-1960: N (Box 191, Folder 4926)
    - 1958-1960: P (Box 191, Folder 4927)
    - 1958-1960: P (Box 191, Folder 4928)
    - 1958-1960: Q-S (Box 191, Folder 4929)
    - 1958-1960: S (Box 191, Folder 4930)
    - 1958-1960: S (Box 191, Folder 4931)
    - 1958-1960: T (Box 191, Folder 4932)
    - 1958-1960: U-V (Box 191, Folder 4933)
    - 1958-1960: W (Box 191, Folder 4934)
    - 1958-1960: Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 4935-4936)
  - Veterans Administration
    - 1961-1964: A-B (Box 192, Folder 4937)
    - 1961-1964: B (Box 192, Folder 4938)
    - 1961-1964: C (Box 192, Folder 4939)
    - 1961-1964: D (Box 192, Folder 4940)
    - 1961-1964: E-F (Box 192, Folder 4941)
    - 1961-1964: G-J (Box 192, Folder 4942)
    - 1961-1964: K-L (Box 192, Folder 4943)
    - 1961-1964: L (Box 192, Folder 4944)
    - 1961-1964: M-N (Box 192, Folder 4945)
    - 1961-1964: P (Box 192, Folder 4946)
    - 1961-1964: R-S (Box 192, Folder 4947)
    - 1961-1964: S (Box 192, Folder 4948)
    - 1961-1964: T-V (Box 192, Folder 4949)
    - 1961-1964: W (Box 192, Folder 4950-4952)
  - Veterans General
    - 1955 (Box 193, Folder 4953-4955)
    - 1956 (Box 193, Folder 4956)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 193, Folder 4957)
    - 1957-1960 (Box 193, Folder 4958)
    - 1961 (Box 193, Folder 4959-4960)
  - Veterans Benefits
    - 1962-1964 (Box 193, Folder 4961)
  - Veterans Hospital: Spokane
    - 1950 (Box 193, Folder 4962-4963)
    - 1947-1950 (Box 193, Folder 4964)
    - 1946-1949 (Box 193, Folder 4965)
    - 1945 (Box 193, Folder 4966)
  - Veterans Hospital: Wenatchee
    - 1944-1945 (Box 194, Folder 4967-4969)
    - 1944 (Box 194, Folder 4970)
  - State Veterans Bonus, 1949-1950 (Box 194, Folder 4971)
  - Veterans Interior, 1943-1945 (Box 194, Folder 4972)
  - Veterans General
    - 1947 (Box 194, Folder 4973)
    - 1948-1950 (Box 194, Folder 4974-4976)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 194, Folder 4977-4978)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 194, Folder 4979-4980)
  - Voice of America, 1947-1948 (Box 195, Folder 4981-4984)
  - War Production Board, 1945 (Box 195, Folder 4985-4988)
  - Weather Bureau
    - 1947-1955 (Box 195, Folder 4989)
    - 1957-1962 (Box 195, Folder 4990)
    - 1958-1962 (Box 195, Folder 4991)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 195, Folder 4992)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 195, Folder 4993)
    - 1957 (Box 195, Folder 4994)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 195, Folder 4995)
    - 1956 (Box 195, Folder 4996)
    - 1947-1955 (Box 195, Folder 4997)
- Series 5: Subject files, 1943-1964
  - Agriculture, Miscellaneous
    - 1948 (Box 196, Folder 4998-5001)
    - 1947 (Box 196, Folder 5002-5007)
    - 1946 (Box 196, Folder 5008)
    - 1945 (Box 196, Folder 5009-5010)
    - 1953 (Box 196, Folder 5011-5014)
    - 1952 (Box 197, Folder 5015-5016)
    - 1951 (Box 197, Folder 5017)
    - 1949 (Box 197, Folder 5018-5020)
    - 1961 (Box 197, Folder 5021-5022)
    - 1954-1960 (Box 197, Folder 5023)
    - 1958-1960 (Box 197, Folder 5024)
    - 1954-1958 (Box 197, Folder 5025)
    - 1954 (Box 197, Folder 5026-5030)
  - Atomic Energy
    - 1957-1958 (Box 198, Folder 5031)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 198, Folder 5032)
    - 1963 (Box 198, Folder 5033)
    - 1957 (Box 198, Folder 5034)
    - 1956 (Box 198, Folder 5035)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 198, Folder 5036)
    - 1954 (Box 198, Folder 5037)
    - 1953, 1962 (Box 198, Folder 5038)
    - 1962 (Box 198, Folder 5039)
    - 1961 (Box 198, Folder 5040)
    - 1960 (Box 198, Folder 5041)
    - 1959 (Box 198, Folder 5042)
    - 1958 (Box 198, Folder 5043-5045)
    - 1950-1952 (Box 198, Folder 5046)
    - 1949 (Box 198, Folder 5047)
    - 1948 (Box 198, Folder 5048)
    - 1947 (Box 198, Folder 5049)
  - Aviation
    - 1950 (Box 199, Folder 5050-5051)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 199, Folder 5052)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 199, Folder 5053)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 199, Folder 5054)
    - 1947 (Box 199, Folder 5055-5057)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 199, Folder 5058)
    - 1946 (Box 199, Folder 5059)
    - 1943-1946 (Box 199, Folder 5060)
    - 1943 (Box 199, Folder 5061-5063)
    - 1955 (Box 200, Folder 5064-5067)
    - 1954 (Box 200, Folder 5068-5069)
    - 1953 (Box 200, Folder 5070-5071)
    - 1953 (Port.-Sea. Service Case) (Box 200, Folder 5072-5074)
    - 1952 (Box 200, Folder 5075-5077)
    - 1951 (Box 200, Folder 5078)
    - 1951 (Box 201, Folder 5079)
    - 1958 (Box 201, Folder 5080-5085)
    - 1957 (Box 201, Folder 5086)
    - 1958 (Box 201, Folder 5087)
    - 1957 (Box 201, Folder 5088-5094)
    - 1956 (Box 202, Folder 5095-5097)
    - 1960 (Box 202, Folder 5098-5103)
    - 1959-1961 (Box 202, Folder 5104)
    - 1959 (Box 202, Folder 5105-5106)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 202, Folder 5107)
    - 1964 (Box 203, Folder 5108)
    - 1963 (Box 203, Folder 5109-5112)
    - 1962 (Box 203, Folder 5113-5117)
    - 1961 (Box 203, Folder 5118-5121)
  - Budget, Cost of Living, National Debt
    - 1952 (Box 204, Folder 5122-5123)
    - 1951 (Box 204, Folder 5124-5125)
    - 1950 (Box 204, Folder 5126)
    - 1949 (Box 204, Folder 5127)
    - 1948 (Box 204, Folder 5128)
    - 1947 (Box 204, Folder 5129-5133)
    - 1959 (Box 204, Folder 5134)
    - 1959 (Box 204, Folder 5135-5139)
    - 1959 (continued) (Box 205, Folder 5140)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 205, Folder 5141)
    - 1957 (Box 205, Folder 5142-5149)
    - 1952-1957 (Box 205, Folder 5150)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 205, Folder 5151)
    - 1962 (Box 205, Folder 5152-5155)
    - 1962 (Box 206, Folder 5156)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 206, Folder 5157)
    - 1960, 1963 (Box 206, Folder 5158)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 206, Folder 5159)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 206, Folder 5160)
    - 1961 (Box 206, Folder 5161-5163)
    - 1960 (Box 206, Folder 5164)
    - 1948-1950 (Box 206, Folder 5165)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 206, Folder 5166)
    - 1963 (Box 206, Folder 5167-5170)
    - 1964 (Box 206, Folder 5171)
  - Census
    - 1964 (Box 207, Folder 5172)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 207, Folder 5173)
    - 1961 (Box 207, Folder 5174)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 207, Folder 5175)
    - 1950 (Box 207, Folder 5176)
    - 1944-1949 (Box 207, Folder 5177)
  - Chamber of Commerce: Seattle
    - 1947-1948 (Box 207, Folder 5178-5179)
    - 1948 (Box 207, Folder 5180-5181)
    - 1947 (Box 207, Folder 5182-5186)
    - 1950 (Box 207, Folder 5187-5189)
    - 1949 (Box 207, Folder 5190-5191)
    - 1945 (Box 208, Folder 5192-5195)
    - 1943 (Box 208, Folder 5196-5197)
    - 1944 (Box 208, Folder 5198)
    - 1958 (Box 208, Folder 5199)
    - 1959 (Box 208, Folder 5200)
    - 1964 (Box 208, Folder 5201)
    - 1963 (Box 208, Folder 5202)
    - 1962 (Box 208, Folder 5203)
    - 1961 (Box 208, Folder 5204)
    - 1960 (Box 208, Folder 5205)
    - 1959 (Box 208, Folder 5206)
    - 1958 (Box 208, Folder 5207-5208)
    - 1958 (continued) (Box 209, Folder 5209)
    - 1955 (Box 209, Folder 5210)
    - 1956 (Box 209, Folder 5211-5212)
    - 1957 (Box 209, Folder 5213)
    - 1958 (Box 209, Folder 5214)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 209, Folder 5215)
    - 1951-1952 (Box 209, Folder 5216-5217)
    - 1952 (Box 209, Folder 5218-5219)
  - Chamber of Commerce: Seattle, Century 21 exposition
    - 1961-1962 (Box 209, Folder 5220)
    - 1960 (Box 209, Folder 5221)
    - 1959 (Box 209, Folder 5222-5226)
  - Chamber of Commerce: Spokane
    - 1951-1952 (Box 210, Folder 5227)
    - 1964 (Box 210, Folder 5228)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 210, Folder 5229)
    - 1959-1962 (Box 210, Folder 5230)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 210, Folder 5231)
    - 1961 (Box 210, Folder 5232)
    - 1956 (Box 210, Folder 5233)
    - 1955 (Box 210, Folder 5234)
    - 1950 (Box 210, Folder 5235)
    - 1949 (Box 210, Folder 5236)
    - 1948 (Box 210, Folder 5237)
    - 1947 (Box 210, Folder 5238)
    - 1954 (Box 210, Folder 5239-5240)
    - 1953 (Box 210, Folder 5241)
  - Chamber of Commerce: Wenatchee
    - 1953-1960 (Box 211, Folder 5242)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 211, Folder 5243)
    - 1950 (Box 211, Folder 5244)
    - 1949 (Box 211, Folder 5245)
    - 1948 (Box 211, Folder 5246)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 211, Folder 5247)
    - 1952 (Box 211, Folder 5248)
    - 1951 (Box 211, Folder 5249)
    - 1964 (Box 211, Folder 5250)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 211, Folder 5251)
    - 1947 (Box 211, Folder 5252)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 211, Folder 5253)
  - Chamber of Commerce: Miscellaneous
    - 1946-1947 (Box 211, Folder 5254)
    - 1951, 1956, 1961 (Box 211, Folder 5255)
    - 1956 (Box 211, Folder 5256-5257)
  - Chemicals in Foods: Food and Drug Administration
    - 1959 (Box 212, Folder 5258)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 212, Folder 5259)
    - 1962 (Box 212, Folder 5260)
    - 1961 (Box 212, Folder 5261)
    - 1962 (Box 212, Folder 5262-5264)
    - 1961 (Box 212, Folder 5265)
    - 1953 (Box 212, Folder 5266)
    - 1952 (Box 212, Folder 5267)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 212, Folder 5268)
  - Chemicals in Food
    - 1964 (Box 212, Folder 5269)
    - 1963 (Box 212, Folder 5270)
    - 1960 (Box 212, Folder 5271-5272)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 212, Folder 5273)
    - 1959 (Box 212, Folder 5274)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 213, Folder 5275)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 213, Folder 5276)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 213, Folder 5277)
    - 1956-1959 (Box 213, Folder 5278)
    - 1958 (Box 213, Folder 5279-5282)
    - 1958-1960 (Box 213, Folder 5283)
    - 1944, 1947 (Box 213, Folder 5284)
    - 1947-1949 (Box 213, Folder 5285)
    - 1949 (Box 213, Folder 5286)
    - 1948 (Box 213, Folder 5287)
    - 1950 (Box 213, Folder 5288)
    - 1949-1950 (Box 213, Folder 5289)
  - Chemicals in Food: Pesticides
    - 1955-1956 (Box 214, Folder 5290)
    - 1954-1957 (Box 214, Folder 5291-5292)
    - 1951 (Box 214, Folder 5293)
    - 1953 (Box 214, Folder 5294)
    - 1954 (Box 214, Folder 5295-5297)
    - 1953 (Box 214, Folder 5298-5302)
  - Civil Defense
    - 1963-1964 (Box 215, Folder 5303)
    - 1963 (Box 215, Folder 5304)
    - 1962 (Box 215, Folder 5305-5306)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 215, Folder 5307)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 215, Folder 5309)
    - 1959 (Box 215, Folder 5309-5310)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 215, Folder 5311)
    - 1957 (Box 215, Folder 5312-5313)
    - 1951-1955 (Box 215, Folder 5314)
    - 1951 (Box 215, Folder 5315-5316)
  - Civil Rights
    - 1963 (Box 216, Folder 5317)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 216, Folder 5318)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 216, Folder 5319)
    - 1960-1962 (Box 216, Folder 5320)
    - 1948-1953 (Box 216, Folder 5321)
    - 1963 (Box 216, Folder 5322)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 216, Folder 5323)
    - 1963 (Box 216, Folder 5324-5326)
    - 1964 (Box 216, Folder 5327)
    - 1963 (Box 216, Folder 5328-5332)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 216, Folder 5333)
    - 1964 (Box 217, Folder 5334-5338)
    - 1963 (Box 217, Folder 5339-5345)
    - 1964 (Box 217, Folder 5346-5348)
    - 1963-1964 (Box 217, Folder 5349)
  - Claims, private
    - 1953 (Box 218, Folder 5350)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 218, Folder 5351)
    - 1952 (Box 218, Folder 5352)
    - 1951 (Box 218, Folder 5353-5355)
    - 1950 (Box 218, Folder 5356-5357)
    - 1949 (Box 218, Folder 5358-5360)
    - 1948 (Box 218, Folder 5361)
    - 1947 (Box 218, Folder 5362-5365)
    - 1946 (Box 218, Folder 5366)
    - 1945 (Box 218, Folder 5367-5372)
    - 1944-1946 (Box 218, Folder 5373)
    - 1964 (Box 218, Folder 5374)
    - 1962-1963 (Box 218, Folder 5375)
    - 1964 (Box 218, Folder 5376)
    - 1963 (Box 218, Folder 5377)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 218, Folder 5378)
    - 1962 (Box 218, Folder 5379-5380)
    - 1961 (Box 218, Folder 5381-5382)
    - 1961 (continued) (Box 219, Folder 5383-5384)
    - 1960 (Box 219, Folder 5385)
    - 1958 (Box 219, Folder 5386)
    - 1957 (Box 219, Folder 5387)
    - 1950-1956 (Box 219, Folder 5388)
    - 1960 (Box 219, Folder 5389)
    - 1959 (Box 219, Folder 5390-5391)
    - 1958 (Box 219, Folder 5392-5393)
    - 1957 (Box 219, Folder 5394)
    - 1956 (Box 219, Folder 5395-5396)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 219, Folder 5397)
    - 1956 (Box 219, Folder 5398)
    - 1949-1955 (Box 219, Folder 5399)
    - 1947 (Box 219, Folder 5400)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 219, Folder 5401)
    - 1954 (Box 219, Folder 5402-5403)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 219, Folder 5404)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 219, Folder 5405)
    - 1955 (Box 219, Folder 5406)
    - 1954 (Box 219, Folder 5407-5409)
  - Claims: William S. Williams
    - 1960-1964 (Box 220, Folder 5410)
    - 1960 (Box 220, Folder 5411)
    - 1958-1960 (Box 220, Folder 5412)
    - 1963 (Box 220, Folder 5413)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 220, Folder 5414)
    - 1952-1956 (Box 220, Folder 5415)
    - 1949-1952 (Box 220, Folder 5416)
    - 1952 (Box 220, Folder 5417)
  - Customs
    - 1956 (Box 220, Folder 5418)
    - 1951-1953 (Box 220, Folder 5419)
    - 1956 (Box 220, Folder 5420)
    - 1955 (Box 220, Folder 5421-5422)
    - 1954 (Box 220, Folder 5423-5425)
    - 1953 (Box 220, Folder 5426-5427)
    - 1952 (Box 220, Folder 5428)
    - 1951 (Box 220, Folder 5429)
    - 1955 (Box 220, Folder 5430)
    - 1952-1954 (Box 220, Folder 5431)
    - 1955 (Box 220, Folder 5432)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 220, Folder 5433)
    - 1955 (Box 220, Folder 5434)
    - 1949-1952 (Box 221, Folder 5435)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 221, Folder 5436)
    - 1953 (Box 221, Folder 5437-5441)
    - 1953 (Box 221, Folder 5438)
    - 1952 (Box 221, Folder 5442)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 221, Folder 5443)
    - 1953 (Box 221, Folder 5444)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 221, Folder 5445)
    - 1952 (Box 221, Folder 5446)
    - 1948 (Box 221, Folder 5447)
    - 1947 (Box 221, Folder 5448)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 221, Folder 5449)
    - 1947 (Box 221, Folder 5450)